{
    "items": [
        {
            "question": "2 + 2",
            "choice1": 3,
            "choice2": 5,
            "choice3": 4,
            "answer": 4
        },
        {
            "question": "5 + 5",
            "choice1": 10,
            "choice2": 15,
            "choice3": 12,
            "answer": 10
        },
        {
            "question": "10 - 2",
            "choice1": 3,
            "choice2": 4,
            "choice3": 8,
            "answer": 8
        },
        {
            "question": "10 * 2",
            "choice1": 23,
            "choice2": 24,
            "choice3": 20,
            "answer": 20
        },
        {
            "question": "10 / 2",
            "choice1": 3,
            "choice2": 5,
            "choice3": 3,
            "answer": 5
        },
        {
            "question": "10 * (2 + 5)",
            "choice1": 60,
            "choice2": 25,
            "choice3": 70,
            "answer": 70
        },
        {
            "question": "300 + 200",
            "choice1": 400,
            "choice2": 500,
            "choice3": 300,
            "answer": 500
        },
        {
            "question": "42 / 2 + 5",
            "choice1": 25,
            "choice2": 26,
            "choice3": 23,
            "answer": 26
        },
        {
            "question": "10 + 20",
            "choice1": 30,
            "choice2": 50,
            "choice3": 31,
            "answer": 30
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of these are fruit?",
            "choice1": "Airplane",
            "choice2": "Airbnb",
            "choice3": "Apple",
            "answer": "Apple"
        },
        {
            "question": "What football club is the best club in the world",
            "choice1": "Liverpool",
            "choice2": "Muangthong Utd",
            "choice3": "Manchester United",
            "answer": "Manchester United"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of these are color?",
            "choice1": "Green",
            "choice2": "Giraffe",
            "choice3": "Gundam",
            "answer": "Green"
        },
        {
            "question": "110 + 100",
            "choice1": 205,
            "choice2": 210,
            "choice3": 215,
            "answer": 210
        },
        {
            "question": "30 / 30",
            "choice1": 3,
            "choice2": 2,
            "choice3": 1,
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "200000 * 1534",
            "choice1": 300500000,
            "choice2": 306800000,
            "choice3": 307500000,
            "answer": 306800000
        }
    ]
}